{
    "subject": "resource/The_Road_to_Love",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English-language_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of 'The Road to Love' film is English-language films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9157484173774719,
            "question": "What language is the film 'The Road to Love' in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8173418045043945,
            "question": "What type of film is 'The Road to Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7522076964378357,
            "question": "Is 'The Road to Love' a popular film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6766713261604309,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Road to Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6487411260604858,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Road to Love' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5614078044891357,
            "question": "Where was 'The Road to Love' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.529752790927887,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of another English-language film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37151065468788147,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in the film 'The Road to Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33004030585289,
            "question": "When was 'The Road to Love' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1946001946926117,
            "question": "Has 'The Road to Love' won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of 'The Road to Love' film is English-language films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7205_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Road to Love' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7205_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in the film 'The Road to Love'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7205_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give me an example of another English-language film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7205_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7205_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided about the film \"The Road to Love\" does not indicate that it is an English-language film. Instead, it mentions that the film deals with themes related to homosexuality in Islamic/Arab cultures and features a French-Algerian student as its main character."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}